Hello friends, I am Chandan Patel and
today I am going to talk about a company
which is the market leader. There is
no such company in India
that can
break its record. Look, the name of the company
is ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited and if we
talk about its market capitalization, then
its market capitalization is 674,500 crores.
If I talk about its current market
price, then it is 1484. But look, if I talk about 52-week high
and 52-week low, then you
can see here that
this arrow is approximately ₹800 per kg and for
gun juice, it is ₹1529. And if I
talk about the back of this stock, then
its price is 48.8500. If I talk about its book value, then
see, the rate of book value is
154 rupees. Look, if I
talk about the dues, then it is 0.24 percent.
If I talk about the accused, then it is 209 points
per note.  Of
and health, if I talk about face value, then the
face value is 10, if I go
down a little in this topic, then see,
if we talk about quarterly results,
you see here,
its net profit was 232 crores in December 2017,
212 crores in March 2018, 219 crores in June 2018, 293 crores
in September 2018,
293 crores in December 2018,
228 crores in March 2019,
310 crores in June 2019, if we talk about September 2019, then
360 crores, if we talk about December 2019, then
294 crores and see, in March 2019, the
net profit here is about 282 crores
and see how tremendously
Islam has accumulated in the wheat period,
if we talk about June 2019, then the
net profit is about 398 crores, if we look at the pocket
Profit and Loss: If we talk about this device, then
look here, in 2009, there used to be a
net profit of only Rs 24 crore
and even now, if I talk about March 2010, there was a
huge boom and
look here, it is very based, yes, we can see
and look here, there is a
net profit of Rs 100 crore and if we talk about 2011, then
in March 2012, there is a
net profit of Rs 353 crore in 2013, Rs
520 crore in March 2014 and Rs
585 crore in March 2015, Rs 505 crore in March 2016, Rs
700 crore in March 2017, if we
talk about March 2018, then Rs 862 crore was seen,
in March 2019, Rs 1000 crore, Rs
49 crore and then after this,
if I talk about March 2019, there is a
net profit of Rs 1194 crore here,
now look.  If we compare it with about two years ago, then
see
how tremendous it is, I mean if we do it after 10-11 years, then there is a
tremendous jump here.
If we talk about the share holding pattern, then
look at the share holding pattern of
December 2016, if we compare it with now, then
you see here in September-December
2017, 55 point note,
here they have
a folding note of SM and if we talk about f5, then if we
talk about 500 devices, then 98100 and if we
talk about public, 2804, here they have
stake, if we talk about motor, then
see, even now they have
units, here they have holding and if we
talk about f5, see brother, the stock has
increased because if
we compare from 2017 to 2020, then they have
picked up a lot of stock, 27 points
and 10 and here if we do it after this,
see in December 2017, 9477,
so here  But our stage was now, look at your
points, here they have a stake of 5980,
if we talk about the public, then the public has
removed a huge small amount,
they have a stake of 7.42, let me
take you to another website and there we will see
how the situation is developing there,
Techie Vivek has come to another website
and see here it is 26 rupees 65 paise,
you can see the rise of about 1.83 percent here
and if I talk about this stock,
see this stock is currently in police trend
and here if I talk about its one
plate which is being told here,
see here 10 people are positive and one person is just
saying negative and if I
talk about its return, then you
see its return in about 3 years,
here the return is 90 percent, out of 2 years there is
limited tax return
and if we go down a little, then
look here,
I will find you on the share holding
pattern and we go to the share holding pattern and
see here, but the
measurement on this share  The holder is
with the promoter, see the pledged shares are nothing,
if we talk about mutual funds,
see money is invested in about 33 schemes,
they have 10
point five percent voting, if we
talk about f5, then 614 f5 have invested here,
they have approximately
127 point 1% in quality
and see here if we talk about other instruments,
they have holding of 3.0 6% here
and non-institutional
investors, see here seven point
one photo of the send folding goes to them,
then I take you to the chart and
there we see how the situation is on the chart,
see this film, now we will go ahead and
see the situation here, on 24th December, it had
made a high of about Rs 1495 and the same, its
high was made recently, now
see, it was made recently,
if I talk about 2nd December, it had made Rs 1530,
if I believe this
and by believing this  See, if I
talk about the stock, if I talk about this
stock which is a little hot, then see here
when it had made this low in the long gown around
16th March, if I talk about that, then in that week it had
made around ₹800
and then from here I got to see a rise in this stock,
see whose fit
level was this which it could not cross, then
after going here, see
after 10th August, the stock was seen to go down a little here
and then after that
as soon as this stock went down from here, then a
rise from here near it was seen in which a very
fast rise was seen
in this stock and this created
level of it was broken here, it
is okay in it and a little correction was seen in it,
again a little correction was seen in this stock,
but if you see, if
I feel that if this level is a little
then there is a very good possibility of it going up, so
if you take entry here, then if
you take entry with stop loss, then
you can get a good cup chunri
You know that Pfizer has
come into its market and has made a lot of changes
because they needed the goods, that is why
they sold the goods and then bought the goods after that, so that is why
I say friend that if
you want to invest in this stock then you
can invest here, you will make good
money and see, I am
saying to use it because it has
almost broken the level created by it
and if you want to wait a little more then
you should wait for it for about fifteen hundred and fifty
rupees,
that if this level of fifteen hundred and fifty rupees is
broken then you can take interest here and
you should put a stop loss of 15030 rupees here,
as if this stock will
try to run above ₹15050 and ₹16100,
then you should increase your stop loss to about 15050 or
1555 rupees and as this stock
increases, you keep increasing your stop loss behind so
that you avoid getting launched
and 110 very good you should put this  But I got pinches
and I think that if it
breaks the level of 1550 then you will
see a very strong rise in it and it will
try to touch the stop of around 2000, it will definitely touch the stop of around 1968 2000,
thank you friends and whenever you
invest here, invest with stop loss.